Yes, read it, salute to the readers, Sat Sri Akal,
Chhotu's blessings and lots of love to everyone,
good morning and thank you from the bottom of my heart and
today I welcome you with
some information for you people, along with that there will be for the
ODI series, which has been
applied for a plot based in Chief, the
process has been completed, the
process of which is going to be done now, so let us
know what is it for this, so first of all
I want to tell you that there is a
youth in which it is written that
aloe vera has been disabled
because you are on the digital service portal,
hi, its that is,
our
single IS single virus device in the name of single biometrics, that
add device denial mode has been turned on from the digital service portal,
hence this
process of their static IP has been disabled,
this is what Anurag Singh ji says,
maintenance of which is mostly done by the rich in Dhar
and he does it so
that he and for this, please try
so that we can complete the further process, so
it is very important if you help him, the
appointment process will be completed and
You can see it in the video by
subscribing to the channel. In this video, I am going to
tell you,
first of all, what is written in it about getting the
stadium audited, first of all I will
tell you how to deal with the traffic problem, how to
proceed with it by being a little tennis club, secondly I will tell you
that if you want the fingerprint of the changer virus, then
you have two options,
but here it is written that you have
not ordered from that hotel, so
some such issue has happened and many times it has happened,
whose is it, if on the other hand, if
I have a single IS divided device of the old company or any other company, then can it
work in the device, then look, on the
contrary, very carefully, this thing needs to be understood
and it is very important that it is
not necessary that the device is given on the service portal, what
I mean to say is that
if you take a single virus device, then that
single artist device should be STQC approved,
we have a standard testing department,
as I will
see the old videos in the previous video, then the situation in it
All the reverses have been explained about it,
so please wash it once
and whatever this thing is,
whether it is of Mantra, whether it is gutkha, whether it is of any
company, whether it is of any company, I will
share the name of that company, what is this back on the Digital Seva Portal,
there is a particular
biometric amount, the brand of the company,
which is coming in the latest updates, which
I had ordered, if
you go to Bhagat Ka Rishta Seva Portal, then
let me show you, first of all I will
show you that the device is 11th, so
you go to the hotel and
log in, now the one which is
behind you is Gehlot,
whatever is your password, you will enter it, you will do a
simple login, watch the video on your Vishwa Seva
Portal, please do not do this, the
video is very romantic for you, there will be
no problem in the future, you have to
come to your Digital Seva Portal in a simple way and after it comes in the box, when you enter it in
PVC, you either enter it by clicking
or you enter it by clicking on either
of the two  Look, if I enter my device, the
same page will open, then
security device, and if I go
under PC, the same page will open, where will I regret it,
after clicking, you can enter it at the bottom,
and here, see
where the sugar of these biometric devices is coming,
after that you will see here,
biometric devices, pimple powder,
difficult election voter, this is another matter,
biometric devices, printers and
Sanjay Dutt, click on this, now here you will
see that if someone is doing
your respectable business of Aadhar card, then
he can do it, if someone
wants Magic TVC Aadhar card printer, he can buy it,
if someone wants to use Magic cutting board etc.,
you can take the animal part, you can see the ribbon of the forms
and on the stage of the stock, like the mode,
and this is the service device of Mantra, similarly it has a
hinge, you
can do this here, and in this, the
scanner organized festival, single ID scan, Ajay Singh
scanner, I am talking about the same, which
was the first brand  That was it but the company will remain the same but the
accused brand name earlier it is now
accused and it is generated from the machine like this
and along with it like in the printer
if you have a printer and like forest
rights you correct it which is the other one
which you can keep in your computer or laptop
then this subscription is
coming and the second one is that there is a
type of four table affordable one, it has
a circle like shape and
you have to mix it with the proper circle
so that after you place a customer
his proper focus is inside this machine and
this machine is used in rough practical,
I use it in between big installations,
how many Singh's pain have actually been
sold, so I saw that
you address this IS like this,
priority is very good from everyone, so it was that the
person who has clarity wife, let me tell you
what is this Singh Arise, that this
mail has come that after a period the
investor has become that the wife of you has made this Reddy
clean bold but it has happened because due to
which he has not done the photo scenery scooter,
so see this  It is not necessary that it will
save the photo inside only then you will click on it,
if you have pressed the proper button from somewhere
else, due to which
I had just done this shopping within 15-16 days,
she was
showing you some video that my product has arrived
and this product of 1 month, this moral
education, how did it happen again
that I used to face problem and when I talked to ma'am,
she said that
I had to leave this deposit due to stories and images,
but after the first shift, all that
happened from Amazon in the middle of 18 years 2017, I had someone within three days, if the
sim is divided then I have to
take or give the device, it is
not necessary for me to visit the digital service portal,
so if someone has this mixed after the butterfly
and is watching this video, then
my request to them is
that you drop a mile
to China and China Gaurav ji for
this more support  Ji ko saiya Anurag,
you have all these fairs, if you shoot with other people, then you get continuous
updates from everyone, if you do
n't come then Anurag ji has a fair,
go to the state's mail and you click
and you will see that in China, many
people also used to type,
so you can also send them ms word and
write to them, if you have
this biometrics device, single sided device, then if
you want to try it somewhere, then
definitely make a small video of it with his heart and his ex, how has it come to
me,
show me your video like this, please sir, my name is my
CID, I am telling you a very unique thing
which is very important, you have to
understand it carefully, you have a color
device and did not do it out of fear and
that is why if you want a test, because
what will he do, your express horizon is that
he loves Anurag or
anyone, he will first see that you have
registered everything, you have
registered the machine in it, then that
sex will not work in which that big machine has
gone which gives us my  It used to be of all five fingers,
earlier in Athani comment, it was done
in coordination or test match that you
need only season IS putting device and you
need only service service device, so if you have
channel A, B and C of the house, it also said that if
you have worked in old Kabira and you
have heart then please do not use it, yes you can
use more personal in now, you can keep it
and you can sticker, if
you have any third or fourth then you can do that also
and what will be the condition in this, it was
told to you in this video, this sticky C is
towards certified Aadhar,
so you should first know about it, if you should do
this then first of all go to the website of that company and
see whether it is an
institute or not, there are two,
three or four companies which sir, guest,
eminent person, it seems new or old here,
now this is the tree
of biometrics, inside the packing, this
entire device was same, the package and its
brand is from the soil, so towards C  The
tree that I was living in came in long and skin,
I have it, so
this also has a nice smell, I went and
looked on the government website and when I
looked on this website, there is only
proper Aadhar and chicken which is considered a coriander
and apart from that
you can also take Praful, other one, Mantra etc.,
whatever you take, be careful about it, but
I would like to
tell you that it is very important that
one word is wrong, that it is not necessary that the
device should be bought from your back side, girls, by turning
on the free mode in this device, from your salary
or from some different jersey or two tomatoes
and that is because it is a life
product and there is a serial number on the back of it,
whenever you register it,
this number has to be removed by five physical of o'clock
and it becomes one and there is a
fast, so whenever you have time,
you should consider that she has
made a small person of your own with her son,
show her your love and my name is
given behind me and I have given it to these
tips at that time  I was doing this and I
tried it well and it was like this
and you can also show that heart in the video
and it was good by doing it and then after that
Tamira like sound, you can use it in my
email message side, the person's date which comes from
this bag, some
ordinary A great you idiot had come from talking, you
also type that in it,
where did he get his education, it was from Vikramshila from Dhar
and this is my cigarette, because of this
you adopt the quantity of the table sticker, you
shared this photo with me, that is
why he folded it, he was doing
research there, so if you have
75 from there and you receive the broad which has the
record of World War, this
captive power device or not, look, Syed's
software has been made, the recipe has been
made well, that this
device does it because when we
take a double device, some changes happen in the same hour, it is
possible that the plastic will suffer a little differently,
when it doubles and it will become
high down and for 5 minutes, then this
suicide pass is so that  We have one Aadhar card,
this day it is only and only for this, it can be of
interest, it can do good work, so
let's work on these things,
this red practitioner is for saliva, so you
have all that emergency, make a small
chakli and scan it and send it to window 7
Munni, along with this
you take this device in your hand and you will
see on the back side below it, there is its free
number, send the problem along with the proof
which will be in a strong room, when City
Mukul Dwivedi will verify it,
we will check if this device is violated and it is
correct, then he will just give you the acidity voice
and then your further process will
start, this was some special
thing, worry and as far as the device is concerned,
we have the device ready, that's all, a lot of
comments come from many people from mission schools that I
can use it, I would just say that whoever is feeling
Chinese job has to nurture that device, no
matter how you do
chatting and its network never
keeps asking what is the cost for it  I would have definitely
shared it with you, I would have informed you, I have removed it.
Now come, let me take you to those
rural areas where those who do not have a static IP,
many people had fitted their dynamic
IP in it. Later, when
Gaurav ji wrote what he had said, then I
found out that friend, hey brother Ajay, I will remember it, if I enter it
wrong, then there is
no need to worry about it, it will
just take a little time, keep this in
mind, if you
have a static IP then it is
okay, the solution is there, I
told you a little about it in this video
that if there is any issue
related to static IP, you can do that too,
so first of all search it on Google and it
is quite clear, however, first of all
you should look on the right side, the
customer care number is written here, so you should
call from it, see, those who are from BT,
those are in big cities where they are
getting good internet related services,
so for them, these
BTs who are from valleys rural areas, so
You can see the entire vote bank correction in India,
you can also get it through Bhagya BSL
or farm, if there is
any other poison around your house, then you can get it straight for several
kilometers, especially for the situation, you have to tell the people a
little something
from the middle of the uniform faculties, whatever details have to be told in short,
I make a small four-five
minute The Flying Jatt video and
share it with you, but in which
I feel that he needs to tell you this,
for that I make a little longer video, I
make a little number in
which I can explain to you in detail, take
care of things, explain
that you should show the solution to infection and your work properly,
and all this is the love of all of you
and he maintains the feet and
stay tuned to this channel, so if you are from the
entire area, then
come to this website and if there is a proper email ID here, then
you edit the email from your research officer in this,
you call this customer care number
and on calling the customer care number, do the one
which is registered for you on the service portal, that is,
whoever gives his secret
in it  He calls from the same number
that he entered and will be able to click on it to
record the city after that he will be
able to see all the things here so if you are in the area then
what is there is very important,
you will have to make some expenses, there will be some investment
and along with that investment you will
also get the right to earn, it will become a
means for you to earn, if there is
internet connection in your area then CAA
Wi-Fi Chaupal means India will
knock at your door through Test Cricket,
Ravi Shankar Prasad Singh who is our
administrator, for
half an hour Varun said what has happened to him
and once you deliver this research unit certificate to our Ag Digital,
our Ravi Shankar, you are seeing,
we will be very grateful to him, this is a
very good work for our country, he is doing a lot of
good for Amazon India, so
you go there and point all your things to
him and that basically I once had to get it for
someone in
this Punjabi,
I spoke to him in Allahabad, whether he took it
or not, he did not tell me anything and it lasted for 15
minutes  Earlier, bacterial contacted me
when I had launched this tube channel
but I thought that now I will have to create another channel
so that they and they
apart from this, look, I will give this
monk for Greece by soaking in the team on this channel, in the
coming time, people can
apply for PAN card, Aadhar card, passport card
or any other online
form, you must have seen many times that Delhi
Police's SSC form is being filled, so the
phone of Delhi Police has become
through SSC, and that sex is coming very busy,
earlier there was SSC platform and
website for shops, when will the Delhi Police form be changed, but I have warned you
that it has become very expensive, on this occasion, to
which tempered glass is available,
now who eats it,
I am so much this thing, so for this and
our team should do that, apart from this,
Yogendra from our head will be very helpful for them
that they will be able to pin their phone sitting at home,
you will come after submitting your passport, so
everything will also be a little  It is disturbing and
in the coming time, you will keep getting information about
technical things on non-satellite channels of Digital Greatest
so that it will be
available in it that what entries,
how to deal with it and in the world of internet, in this
world, you have to keep yourself
safe from cyber crime, so the
reminder question that you had for Chaupal is confusing, it must have been resolved, it must have been resolved
that we will have a
monthly meeting and you will say some amount to
give you a security amount on this occasion and
what is the security amount, you should
assume that it is refundable and you will be
given some dividend in it and some machines
etc. will be pushed behind it, if
your
quality is actually used then it will go to
you, then you can keep it, so for this it is
necessary that you call here,
contact the callers directly from Chowpatty, if
our Bharat
Net team from China contacts them, they will
convey it to you immediately, this is what Ravi Shankar Prasad
says in Marathi.  This is the topic and all this is to
say that it should reach the villages, so it is
important to reach the villages, if you
subscribe, then you are appointed to add here, then
you should subscribe to this video a
little, I am who is the
I have told you in this video
that if those who have old stickers, it is
simple for them to purchase the device
from the digital service portal, if they have not purchased toys from Kabir and posters, then
they will
come in the situation inside, if I
talk to you about welcome, then the staff appointed in that list will
change you, so in
15-16 days, the day you are very far away, it may happen, the
time of 15-2010 may come and a
little bit of this post of 3960, at that time I got a
single figure ad device and if
you see it now, then its meaning is that with
increasing eyes, I have got a device of ₹100 or so and so many of
their devices, so if we look at it online, then it will be a
little expensive for me, it will be 1000-2000 rupees,
around 5,000, so you might have seen this a little bit and  This
GPS device will keep the network here, so it is
that the secretary
can be photoshopped and it will be fixed with you soon, so
you have to see that you have to make
it public soon, along with the electricity bill,
make that bigg boss economic small card and mail it to him, I was
not talking about yesterday, I am Kishan, you have an elegant
look, your work will definitely be good, if the voice is good then you will
definitely work, secondly you need that
now in the next video I will
tell you the file, this video will be very long,
your answer through which you must have
logged in to that portal, it is being
asked in it at this time, so you enter
your profit and everything in that time and the
location of your center will be asked in it, so
enter the section which you had sent in your Aadhar inspiration form after
scanning it, which
you had entered under the mission,
that proper of the center is there in it and if your CT will
come to Rashmi ji's fair or any ATM
for your welfare department letter, then in that, your center
's number will be put curd in it, we
click on this, if you should have a sim in everything,
if you have an alarm  Who is scared for Shailendra Singh, in that
your back should be because of the
fear of the center, you must have
logged in to any secretary portal today, on
30th August, under the influence of the total of the festival,
that you are one, they are asking for a little survey, in
this Shankar has all the details, he will
ask about you, so you put all the settings
information on the mother and submit it
and along with this, if you
liked the video, then please
like the video and tell the committee your opinion and
if I like it then I will subscribe and
you people feel a little motivational for me, I will be
informative for you, I take out this time and
come for you people because
you know that in this life every person is
very busy in his business and his family, he is not able to type,
still I take out time for you, so
this is my love for all of you, so
please keep giving this love like what, till then take
special care of your service, children and horses, wash your
hands with soap or do not open the app if you get cut in the wound in this row
Clean and wash with sanitizer
and take utmost care of cleanliness in the house
and follow other distances,
if you have very important work to do outside the house, then
if it is not important work then
please do not go out and even if important work is done outside the house then also make a little
effort, keep your face
well protected, keep glasses in your hands
and do it the most in your family, if there is a
mother in the house then
you are her mother-in-law or those with whom you have
spent your life, I would request
everyone to stay inside the house to such an extent and
in this year there is such a question that in India and
in the whole world, the whole world,
New India, the whole world of
humans is second to this one and a half inch of ours
It is important that you stay in this business and house together
with your friends with
love and affection and keep
meeting anyone so that you do
not use anything obscene or anything from your mother or from here which may hurt
anyone's heart, fill everyone with love and
courage and with resignation,
respect everyone, keep the system of everyone,
look at your life, when did the war happen, that this
time that is passing is
never coming back in life, the time that is there
in life, with that time you
and your gurus, your family
and your loved ones will get even, so
use the quantity of Dishoom New Delhi with respect to your highest, the fattest Seth and take respect because
life is what you are, life, no one
knows lightly, so be careful,
keep your vegetables at your center, if I
verify this, the people who are coming,
stick a small label outside your center, it is
war
and if this does not happen then you people
in the normal market, if you are
found positive in bulk then you should fast for four to five hours
No, if it is simply a good spectacle
then you can make a purchase from someone's evil eye,
you get
₹10 for ₹54, that is why you are lying with people, so
if I tell you to click a little on social media then
you can buy a piece of meat and
keep it with you, you will get ₹5 for ₹4,
you are clearly making a profit under Chinese occupation,
okay, so look at my center
that I had clicked on it a lot,
here you saw that at that time three and a half to four times the
cloth keeps on happening on the other track, I
ate meat, Kabir stock, this is it, so about that, from
there I picked up positive Khalini 5300
from the account mother, so they put me on
15-16 thousand sixteen seventeen rupees, Kushan,
it has to be kept in the galaxy itself, so even after
taking it from here 2 minutes ago, my passengers and there
are and a proper heavy sentence, see to yourself and the
people there, how to
do it, keep Gautam ji ready because now
in someone else's digital service portal today  In the
survey that came, this thing has been
asked in a very important manner and this
cotton text is whether you get sanitizers done,
whether the signal allows people to come and go, keeps
setting its own,
then all these things are very important, at that time
they listen to change the formatting in it and you
people develop it in between, so
you need notifications, sorry sorry, I
definitely call you a little bit in your, Flipkart, when
I feel that I have to
tell you some things in detail, then I would have made it
longer in a video so that if I
tell you some things and tell you some more, then it becomes easy for
you, then it is
very important to know that if you have an A machine for social distancing in vegetables and spinach,
if
possible, then you will be given Rs. 3000, 3000, 4000, the
mission comes, which you saw
today, if we talked about Anmol etc., then your
Amazon, then by doing this your company would have been checked,
then we discussed Chinese playlist
because I am telling you one of my things that
this thing will happen that
Paytm of Pleasure will redeem it a lot  There will
be discussions in this video and with this video
you should continue watching the video, when it gets long then you will
see it, then you will
not understand all these things, what is happening,
keep one side in mind that help